<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Arpit Pathak</title><link>https://hold7door.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Arpit Pathak</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Copyright notice</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hold7door.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Implementing domain based Multi-tenancy - 1</title><link>https://hold7door.github.io/posts/post-3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://hold7door.github.io/posts/post-3/</guid><description>In normal scenerios, you build a web-application and host it on a server. Then you purchase a domain which you then link to this server&amp;rsquo;s IP. Other users can then access the web-application using this domain of yours.
However, often times you also want to give the users the ability to map their own domains to a web application which is hosted on a server which you control. Now the users can open the web-application on their own domains as well.</description></item><item><title>Maximum Gap</title><link>https://hold7door.github.io/posts/post-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://hold7door.github.io/posts/post-2/</guid><description>Problem Given an unsorted array, find the maximum difference between the successive elements in its sorted form.
Constraints All elements in the array are non-negative integers and fit in the 32-bit signed integer range.
Solution On first look one can notice that it is easy to solve this problem in O(nlogn) time by first sorting the array and finding maximum difference between consecutive numbers.
Now think about if you were asked to solve this in O(n) time, where n is length of array</description></item><item><title>Kickstart Round G 2020 Combination Lock</title><link>https://hold7door.github.io/posts/post-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://hold7door.github.io/posts/post-1/</guid><description>This is a reiteration of the official Editorial supported with code. Link to Problem -Combination Lock. I would suggest you to read the original problem statement first before going through this editorial.
Problem Your are given an array of numbers of length W and an integer N. Each number of array, let&amp;rsquo;s say Wi is in range 1 &amp;lt;= Wi&amp;lt;= N. In one move you can select any number from the array and increase/decrease that number by 1, wrapping around between 1 and N.</description></item><item><title>Hey</title><link>https://hold7door.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hold7door.github.io/about/</guid><description>I am Arpit.
I am currently working at Whitepanda where I handle mainly the backend-systems.
I would like to sharing my learnings with you and alongside learn from you as well.
Here I stand, atoms with consciousness, matter with curiosity. A universe of atoms, an atom in the universe.
&amp;ndash; Richard Feynman</description></item></channel></rss>